This street style chowmein can definitely be made at home.
If you pay a little attention, I will get it
ready by the time mom returns from Mokshu Park.
Thinking about it, I took out noodles from the pantry
which were made of healthy meat flour.
Put salt and oil in hot water in a vessel and
keep the noodles for 6-7 minutes.
So I picked up colourful vegetables.
And what is this, salvation has arrived.  Here I
cut the vegetables.  On the other hand, Mokshu also picked up
his knife.  The noodles were
strained.  And first added ginger, garlic and chilli.
Then added all the vegetables one by one.  And just do
n't overcook the vegetables.  To
keep it healthy, I skipped the soy sauce.
Added chili sauce and tomato sauce.  Add salt,
pepper and noodles and mix mix mix.
And these spicy healthy
noodles are ready.  When I
heard praise from my family members, I became doubtful.  When I checked myself, I
found out that you were praising me correctly.